angryape.com 2011-06-05

# Privacy

Last updated: January 1st, 2010

We take your privacy very seriously, and we are committed to maintaining the trust of our users. This Privacy Policy will help you understand what types of personal information we collect about you, and how we use it.

We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time. If we do so, the most recent version will always be available on this page. You should visit this page regularly to stay aware of any changes that we may have made. If you do not agree with any part of this Privacy Policy then you should stop using this website immediately. Your continued use of this website signifies your acceptance of this Privacy Policy.

If you are under 13-years-old and live in the United States of America, you must not use this website and must leave immediately. The content of this website is not intended for children and we do not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13.

If you are under 16-years-old and live in the United Kingdom, you must get your parent or guardian's permission whenever you provide personal information to us. If you do not have this permission, you must not provide us with personal information.

When you register to participate in or receive a service from this website, such as newsletters, competitions or user profiles, we may ask for personal information from you. This may include information such as your email address, name, postal address, date of birth or telephone/mobile number. We may also pass this information to third parties that administer any competitions or other promotions so that they may administer it properly. By entering your details into any relevant fields, you are indicating your consent for this website and applicable third parties to provide you with the services you select.

We use cookies in order to provide a better service to you. A cookie is a small amount of data that is sent to your computer or mobile browser ("collectively, device") and is stored on your device's hard drive. You can choose to accept or decline our cookies within your device. Should you reject cookies from this website, certain services cannot be provided to you and you may not be able to take full advantage of all our features.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve advertisements and these companies may set and access their own cookies on your device. They may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. Their use of their own cookies is subject to their own privacy policies, not this Privacy Policy. Google, as a third-party vendor, uses cookies to serve advertising on this site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve advertising to our users based on their visit to this site and other sites on the internet. You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.co.uk/privacy_ads.html).

We also collect IP addresses (a number that can uniquely identify a specific computer or device on the internet), for use in analysis software in order to enhance your user experience. This information is not used to develop a personal profile of you.

We will take all reasonable care to make sure your personal information is kept private in accordance of this Privacy Policy. We will keep your personal information confidential except where disclosure is required or permitted by law.
